bargainmatch.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy

**Overview**

This website and any associated browser or mobile based applications are powered by Inuvo's BargainMatch software application. 

Inuvo Inc. takes consumer privacy seriously. We are committed to following industry standards, best practices and guidelines relating to the use of consumer information and privacy. Inuvo recognizes and complies with the self regulatory policies of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI). 

This privacy policy is intended to inform consumers about the way Inuvo uses and protects the information we collect about customers and users. Information is collected by Inuvo this website, and across our various Technology Platforms. All use of Inuvo's products and services, as well as visits to our websites, are subject to this privacy policy. 

**Information Collected via the Website**

We collect Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") from Inuvo websites when you choose to provide it to us via an information request form or contact us email. PII is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This includes, but is not limited to, name, postal address, telephone number or email address. For example, you may choose to send us PII about yourself in an email or by completing an online form on an Inuvo website. We use this information only to contact you to respond to your inquiry. Once collected, we will store your PII for a reasonable time for record-keeping purposes and promotional marketing efforts. 

Inuvo collects PII on our websites when you sign up as an Account Holder. Account Holder information collected includes PII necessary to conduct business including, but not limited to, account holder name, phone number, email address, payment information. Payments made to and/or from Inuvo require the provision of and specified collection of additional PII, which may include, but is not limited to, bank account information and credit card numbers. Phone, facsimile, email and/or cell numbers may be used to contact Account Holders as needed. All Account Holder information collected is maintained in a password-protected environment where your passwords are not accessible to any Inuvo employee as they are stored via one-way encryption. 

We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII) via Inuvo websites and our various Technology Platforms. Non-PII **cannot** be used to contact any single person or entity and may include, but is not limited to, IP address, content viewed, ad interaction, interaction with other advertiser websites, browser type, Internet Service Provider, the time/date of your visit to the website, your computer's operating system (e.g., Windows XP), search terms used and other click and browsing behavior. Inuvo uses this information for internal purposes such as to administer our websites, improve and customize our websites, and to understand and analyze how our websites are being used for marketing purposes. See Information Collection and Use for more details. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

We use cookies and web beacons to help manage our websites and analyze usage patterns. Cookies are small packets of data stored on a user's computer that allow sites to recognize the computer when a user revisits a website. Cookies can be used to provide consumer services such as auto login, information delivery and a better understanding of how users interact with the site. These cookies enable sites to customize the site to a user's needs and interests, so that they can be as valuable and relevant as possible. The use of a web beacon allows a website to record that someone has visited a particular webpage, along with additional Non-PII that the website may choose to include with the beacon. 

You are always free to decline cookies. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, erase cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. For more information about cookies and web beacons, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies/. 

**Public Forums**

Inuvo websites make chat rooms, forums, message boards, blogs commentary and/or news groups available to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your PII through these channels. 

**Third-Party Websites**

Inuvo websites may contain links to other websites, including Advertiser offers for Publisher participation. Such websites may use cookies and/or other data collection tools. Inuvo is not responsible for the privacy practices, policies or content of such other websites. Inuvo encourages everyone to read the posted privacy policies whenever interacting with any website to learn more about the privacy practices of that website. Inuvo has no control over the use of information by third-party websites, and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any PII to those websites. 

**Browser or Mobile Applications**

When you use a BargainMatch powered browser application some PII may be required so that you can log into your account to track your rewards earnings. Additionally, unless you opt-out, Inuvo and/or its marketing partners may access the following non-PII data on an Anonymous basis: 

  * the operating system of the computer and the type and version of the browser running on the computer; 
  * the unique identifier of the application running on the computer; 
  * the search text typed in Google, Yahoo! Or Bing; 
  * the search tags embedded by the application; 
  * the mouse-over on search tags embedded by the application; 
  * the clicks on message prompts inserted by the application; and 

We may use this PII and non-PII to do the following: 

  * process and fulfill your rewards transactions; 
  * personalize your experience with targeted advertisements based on your expressed interests; 
  * analyze and improve the effectiveness of the application to provide you and fellow users a better experience. 

You can disable or uninstall any of our applications at any time by going to the extension preferences section of your browser and clicking on disable, uninstall or their equivalents on your browser. If you use an applications on multiple computers or browsers, you will need to repeat these steps for each install. 

**Storage of PII**

All information collected via information request forms or contact us emails is only used to respond to that inquiry. Once collected, we will store your PII for a reasonable time for record-keeping purposes and promotional marketing efforts. 

All Account Holder information collected is maintained in a password-protected environment. This information is used for client/customer service, media delivery, contact, billing-payables and receivables and/or other reporting purposes. 

**Storage of Non-PII**

We maintain Non-PII collected by our technology for up to 180 days. This data includes, but is not limited to, IP address, content viewed, ad interaction, interaction with other advertiser websites, browser type, Internet Service Provider, the time/date of your visit to our websites, your computer's operating system (e.g., Windows XP), search terms used and other click and browsing behavior. 

**Security**

Inuvo uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of information and treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company. 

**Sharing and Disclosure**

We do not sell, rent or share PII collected on Inuvo websites with non-affiliated third parties without your consent. 

Inuvo may share Non-PII collected via our Technology Platforms with third-party service providers whom have contracted with third-party marketing partners, business partners and/or Inuvo clients, and as expressly provided for herein. Similarly, we may enhance the Non-PII collected via our Technology Platforms with Non-PII collected from third-party marketing partners, business partners and/or Inuvo clients. This information cannot be used to contact or identify any person individually. 

We may disclose information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. 

Finally, we may transfer information, including any PII collected via Inuvo websites, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change. 

**Opt-Out of Non-PII Data Collection**

If you'd like to opt-out from having Inuvo collect your anonymous Non-PII information in connection with our Technology Platforms, click the link below. In doing so, Inuvo will place an opt-out cookie on your browser. The opt-out cookie means information will not be collected. If you delete, block or otherwise restrict cookies, or if you use a different computer or Internet browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice. Please note that by clicking on the link below you will be immediately opted out. 

**_Click here to opt-out of Non-PII data collection_** . 

**Opt-Out or Update Your PII**

As an Account Holder, you will only receive email communications from Inuvo for business administration purposes, including website and platform service updates. Any promotional emails you may receive will have an opt-out option within the footer of the email. If you opt-out, you will be removed from the promotional email list, however, as an Account Holder, you will still receive any/all business administration emails applicable to your account. As an Account Holder, you can update your PII through most of our websites yourself by simply logging into your account and modifying your account profile. 

If you have voluntarily submitted your PII via one of our websites through an information request form or contact us email, then you may be receiving promotional marketing communications from Inuvo. 

At any time, you can unsubscribe directly from any of these communications by following the opt-out instructions included within the footer of the communication received. 

If you'd like us to update, correct or delete your PII that you have provided to us, please send your request to us at [privacy@inuvo.com](mailto:privacy@inuvo.com) and we will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt. You can also contact us by mail by writing us at: 

Inuvo, Inc.   
Attn: Marketing and Communications   
1111 Main Street   
Suite 201   
Conway, AR 72032 

**The Right to Change This Policy**

Inuvo reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. 

**Contact Us**

If you have questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@inuvo.com](mailto:privacy@inuvo.com) or by mail at: 

Inuvo, Inc.   
Attn: Marketing and Communications   
1111 Main Street   
Suite 201   
Conway, AR 72032
